- And the background... - I understand.
- Und der Hintergrund... - Ich verstehe.
- The dorayaki... - Yes. I appreciate your support.
- Das Dorayaki ... - Ja. Ich weiß Ihre Unterstützung zu schätzen.
- It needs seasonal factors, too. - Thank you. I'll be in touch.
- Es braucht auch saisonale Faktoren. - Danke. Ich melde mich.
About the text...
Zum Text...
Hey, Soma.
Hey, Soma.
I was on the phone about the Aiya contract.
Ich habe wegen des Aiya-Vertrags telefoniert.
So is your big brother the president?
Ist Ihr großer Bruder also der Präsident?
What?
Was?
Really?
Wirklich?
Come on! Why didn't you tell us?
Komm schon! Warum hast du es uns nicht gesagt?
My brother is nobody to me.
Mein Bruder bedeutet mir nichts.
What about the work I asked you to do?
Was ist mit der Arbeit, die ich Ihnen aufgetragen habe?
F-Frosty...
F-Frosty …
♫ If there were magic ♫
♫ Wenn es Magie gäbe ♫
♫ I would make you sparkle ♫ [Shunta Sono]
♫ Ich würde dich zum Strahlen bringen ♫ [Shunta Sono]
♫ It's nice to get a reward once in a while, isn't it? ♫ [Yumena Yanai]
♫ Es ist schön, ab und zu eine Belohnung zu bekommen, nicht wahr? ♫ [Yumena Yanai]
♫ If I can see your face like warm sunshine ♫
♫ Wenn ich dein Gesicht wie warmen Sonnenschein sehen kann ♫
♫ Even my feelings will start to melt away ♫
♫ Sogar meine Gefühle werden anfangen zu schmelzen ♫
♫ Even the chill of the cold rain ♫ [Naoya Kusakawa, Ryuga Sato]
♫ Sogar die Kälte des kalten Regens ♫ [Naoya Kusakawa, Ryuga Sato]
♫ Maybe I want to feel it with my heart ♫
♫ Vielleicht möchte ich es mit meinem Herzen fühlen ♫
♫ Hey, I've fallen in love! Can't you see? ♫ [Kodai Fujimoto]
♫ Hey, ich habe mich verliebt! Siehst du das nicht? ♫ [Kodai Fujimoto]
♫ If I could just take one more step forward ♫
♫ Wenn ich nur noch einen Schritt nach vorne machen könnte ♫
♫ Could I get closer to your warmth? ♫
♫ Könnte ich deiner Wärme näher kommen? ♫
♫ I wonder how I'll be flavored by you? ♫
♫ Ich frage mich, wie du mich schmecken wirst? ♫
♫ On sleepless nights, while holding hands ♫
♫ In schlaflosen Nächten, beim Händchenhalten ♫
♫ Let's make a wish ♫
♫ Lass uns etwas wünschen ♫
♫ Even the unknown is okay, if I'm with you ♫
♫ Auch das Unbekannte ist okay, wenn ich bei dir bin ♫
[My Frosty Co-worker Is Only Sweet to Me]
[Mein frostiger Kollege ist nur nett zu mir]
Soma-kun, wait!
Soma-kun, warte!
Can we talk?
Können wir reden?
Sorry, I need time alone to think.
Entschuldige, ich brauche Zeit allein zum Nachdenken.
I've made you sad.
Ich habe dich traurig gemacht.
I'm sorry.
Es tut mir Leid.
Soma-kun...
Soma-eins…
Is giving him space all I can do right now?
Ist es im Moment alles, was ich tun kann, ihm Freiraum zu geben?
I'm okay, yes...
Mir geht es gut, ja ...
Soma-san?
Soma, Mr.?
So did something happen between you and Ogata?
Ist zwischen Ihnen und Ogata etwas passiert?
How'd you...
Wie hast du...
You wouldn't grab coffee with me otherwise.
Sonst würdest du nicht mit mir einen Kaffee trinken.
You've actually impressed me for the first time.
Sie haben mich tatsächlich zum ersten Mal beeindruckt.
Hey...
Hey...
Actually...
Eigentlich...
Kotori-san wants something I can't accept.
Kotori-san will etwas, das ich nicht akzeptieren kann.
If she gets hurt by this, I'll...
Wenn ihr dadurch etwas zustößt, werde ich ...
I don't know the details, but if you worry about her,
Ich kenne die Einzelheiten nicht, aber wenn Sie sich Sorgen um sie machen,
then why don't you protect her?
warum beschützt du sie dann nicht?
He's right. By my worry, I ended up hurting her.
Er hat recht. Durch meine Sorge habe ich sie letztendlich verletzt.
Or did I oversimplify things?
Oder habe ich die Dinge zu sehr vereinfacht?
Sorry.
Entschuldigung.
No, thank you.
Nein, danke.
Well, reach out when you want to talk.
Melden Sie sich, wenn Sie reden möchten.
I need to talk with Kotori-san.
Ich muss mit Kotori-san sprechen.
Also...
Auch...
Here.
Hier.
Thanks.
Danke.
I know you're devoted, but aren't you overexerting?
Ich weiß, dass Sie engagiert sind, aber überanstrengen Sie sich nicht?
When I stop, worries take over.
Wenn ich aufhöre, übernehmen die Sorgen die Oberhand.
Did something happen with Soma-kun?
Ist etwas mit Soma-kun passiert?
You two are so obvious.
Ihr zwei seid so offensichtlich.
You turned down the job for him, right?
Sie haben den Job für ihn abgelehnt, richtig?
Maybe you can't tell anyone, but you can talk to me.
Vielleicht kannst du es niemandem erzählen, aber mit mir kannst du reden.
Thank you.
Danke schön.
Hey, what's wrong? Kotori?
Hey, was ist los? Kotori?
You have a fever!
Du hast Fieber!
You were overworking.
Sie haben sich überarbeitet.
Rest up or you won't get better.
Ruhen Sie sich aus, sonst wird es Ihnen nicht besser gehen.
- Thanks for bringing me home. - No problem.
- Danke, dass du mich nach Hause gebracht hast. - Kein Problem.
He's fast.
Er ist schnell.
Who?
WHO?
Don't worry.
Mach dir keine Sorge.
You rest. I'll answer the door.
Ruhen Sie sich aus. Ich öffne die Tür.
I got the stuff you wanted.
Ich habe das Zeug, das du wolltest.
Great, thanks.
Super, danke.
How is Kotori-san?
Wie geht es Kotori-san?
I gave her fever meds, and she's sleeping now.
Ich habe ihr Fiebermittel gegeben und jetzt schläft sie.
If she's still feverish tomorrow, will you take her to the ER?
Wenn sie morgen immer noch Fieber hat, bringen Sie sie dann in die Notaufnahme?
I got it.
Ich habe es.
I have no idea why, but did you talk it over?
Ich habe keine Ahnung, warum, aber haben Sie darüber gesprochen?
Soma-kun, you're frosty, but protect your girlfriend.
Soma-kun, du bist frostig, aber beschütze deine Freundin.
Of course. I promise not to make her sad again.
Natürlich. Ich verspreche, sie nicht wieder traurig zu machen.
I'm counting on you.
Ich zähle auf dich.
Sure.
Sicher.
Are you okay?
Geht es dir gut?
Soma-kun?
Soma-eins?
Why are you here?
Warum bist du hier?
Uehara-san called me.
Uehara-san hat mich angerufen.
Do you want to drink something?
Möchtest du etwas trinken?
I've got some sports drinks.
Ich habe ein paar Sportgetränke.
No, I prefer...
Nein, ich bevorzuge ...
I prefer your hand.
Ich bevorzuge deine Hand.
It's cool yet warm too.
Es ist kühl und doch auch warm.
Oh, Soma-kun.
Oh, Soma-kun.
I'm sorry
Es tut mir Leid
I made you so unhappy.
Ich habe dich so unglücklich gemacht.
I'm really sorry.
Es tut mir wirklich leid.
I really am.
Das bin ich wirklich.
That's my line.
Das ist mein Spruch.
I'm sorry, too.
Es tut mir auch leid.
Soma-kun?
Soma-eins?
Good morning. How are you feeling?
Guten Morgen. Wie geht es Ihnen?
Morning.
Morgen.
After a good rest, I feel much better.
Nach einer guten Erholung fühle ich mich viel besser.
That's good to hear.
Das ist gut zu hören.
Were you here with me all night?
Warst du die ganze Nacht hier bei mir?
Of course.
Natürlich.
Do you feel like eating?
Hast du Lust zu essen?
I'll bring you breakfast.
Ich bringe dir Frühstück.
Thank you.
Danke schön.
[Brand concept, Product photos]
[Markenkonzept, Produktfotos]
Soma-kun... this...
Soma-kun... das...
The website's wire frame for Aiya.
Das Drahtmodell der Website für Aiya.
I created this using your notes as reference.
Ich habe dies anhand Ihrer Notizen als Referenz erstellt.
Sorry if I interfere.
Entschuldigen Sie, wenn ich mich einmische.
I'm still trying to make sense of all this,
Ich versuche immer noch, das alles zu verstehen,
but I shouldn't have made you give up work you wanted.
aber ich hätte Sie nicht dazu zwingen sollen, die Arbeit aufzugeben, die Sie wollten.
Moreover, I'd never want to dim your smile.
Außerdem möchte ich Ihr Lächeln niemals trüben.
Sorry I made things hard for you.
Tut mir leid, dass ich es Ihnen schwer gemacht habe.
If something happens, I will protect you.
Wenn etwas passiert, werde ich dich beschützen.
Oh, thank you, Soma-kun!
Oh, danke, Soma-kun!
I'm sorry, too, for making you sad.
Es tut mir auch leid, dass ich Sie traurig gemacht habe.
Sorry! I'll get you sick.
Tut mir leid! Ich werde dich krank machen.
It's okay. I never catch a cold.
It's okay. I never catch a cold.
Besides, my low body temp is finally an advantage.
Besides, my low body temp is finally an advantage.
You feel so nice and cool.
You feel so nice and cool.
When you're feeling hot, I'll cool you down.
When you're feeling hot, I'll cool you down.
Then when you feel cold, I'll warm you like this.
Then when you feel cold, I'll warm you like this.
Soma-kun, is this...
Soma-kun, is this...
Yes, I made you porridge.
Yes, I made you porridge.
At least learn to make porridge for when Nee-chan is ill.
Lernen Sie wenigstens, Brei zuzubereiten, wenn Nee-chan krank ist.
Did you...
Did you...
I've been practicing since Kairi-san told me.
I've been practicing since Kairi-san told me.
Thank you!
Danke schön!
Thank you, Soma-kun!
Thank you, Soma-kun!
No problem.
Kein Problem.
I'll dig in.
I'll dig in.
So, Kotori-san...
So, Kotori-san...
I'll help you.
I'll help you.
I'll help with Aiya's site.
I'll help with Aiya's site.
Are you sure?
Are you sure?
Let's do more than what my brother asks.
Let's do more than what my brother asks.
Soma-kun...
Soma-eins…
I've got your back.
I've got your back.
I'll protect you.
I'll protect you.
I'm your boyfriend, after all.
I'm your boyfriend, after all.
It's a very cookie-cutter website.
It's a very cookie-cutter website.
Can't you make it more tailored to Aiya?
Can't you make it more tailored to Aiya?
I want people to know at once it's our website.
I want people to know at once it's our website.
ðŸ°Thank you to our lovely Channel Manager: sunoosophy
🍰Thank you to our lovely Channel Manager: sunoosophy
ðŸ¨Thank you to our awesome Chief Segmenter: baepsae29 âœ‚ï¸ maria_lavendula_77, teufelchen_netty_266,
🍨Thank you to our awesome Chief Segmenter: baepsae29 ✂️ maria_lavendula_77, teufelchen_netty_266,
Please take a look at this version then.
Please take a look at this version then.
[Japanese Sweets, Aiya]
[Japanische Süßigkeiten, Aiya]
You want to use me to attract customers?
You want to use me to attract customers?
Aiya's appeal is its people and its products.
Aiya's appeal is its people and its products.
As the president, you blend tradition and modernity.
As the president, you blend tradition and modernity.
This version is a hit with the ladies here, too.
This version is a hit with the ladies here, too.
âœ‚ï¸ squirrelpants_73, lyam_88, morva, mella_74, queen_sung_kyung, juli_ann__
✂️ squirrelpants_73, lyam_88, morva, mella_74, queen_sung_kyung, juli_ann__
ðŸ“ Chief Editor: worthyromance
🍓 Chief Editor: worthyromance
ðŸ’ General Editors: isabellaeldanna, sunoosophy
🍒 General Editors: isabellaeldanna, sunoosophy
ðŸ¦Translation Editor: gioia625
🍦Translation Editor: gioia625
So that means I should prepare to go out there?
So that means I should prepare to go out there?
I like it.
I like it.
I hadn't thought of that.
I hadn't thought of that.
ðŸ§Thank you to Other Languages Moderators, Editors and subtitlers.
🍧Thank you to Other Languages Moderators, Editors and subtitlers.
ðŸ§Thank you to our viewers. May you enjoy sweet treats.
🧁Thank you to our viewers. May you enjoy sweet treats.
First impressions matter most for websites.
First impressions matter most for websites.
Oh?
Oh?
Very well, show me how the online shop works.
Very well, show me how the online shop works.
Yes, Sir.
Ja, Sir.
Moving on then.
Moving on then.
Well...
Also...
It's all good.
It's all good.
Please go ahead and launch the site.
Please go ahead and launch the site.
Great job, everyone!
Great job, everyone!
- Chief, your premium green tea. - Gyokuro tea!
- Chief, your premium green tea. - Gyokuro tea!
- Thanks! - Here you go.
- Thanks! - Here you go.
- We really did it! - Thank you!
- We really did it! - Thank you!
He was so silent at first. I got scared!
He was so silent at first. I got scared!
- He's intense! - Yes, really.
- He's intense! - Yes, really.
Thanks.
Danke.
I've never seen my brother so impressed before.
I've never seen my brother so impressed before.
- He's super hot, too. - Really?
- He's super hot, too. - Really?
Talking about me?
Talking about me?
I'm so glad we got his approval.
I'm so glad we got his approval.
He's hard to please, but you awed him.
He's hard to please, but you awed him.
No, I couldn't have done it without you.
No, I couldn't have done it without you.
You devised ideas and ways to win him over.
You devised ideas and ways to win him over.
He cares deeply about being Aiya's face.
He cares deeply about being Aiya's face.
What's wrong?
Was ist los?
I haven't told you something.
I haven't told you something.
The day you had that fever,
The day you had that fever,
I called my brother.
I called my brother.
Kotori-san will manage your site. I'll handle the system.
Kotori-san will manage your site. I'll handle the system.
Oh, you will?
Oh, you will?
Might as well give it your all, as it'll be your last job there.
Might as well give it your all, as it'll be your last job there.
"My last job"?
"My last job"?
When this is over, you'll return to Kyoto, right?
When this is over, you'll return to Kyoto, right?
You haven't yet repaid Father for raising you.
You haven't yet repaid Father for raising you.
Th-Then once this is all over...
Th-Then once this is all over...
No, I won't go back, never.
No, I won't go back, never.
What? You're not?
What? You're not?
That's right. I'll keep pursuing this job here.
That's right. I'll keep pursuing this job here.
With Kotori-san, I'll build a mind-blowing site.
With Kotori-san, I'll build a mind-blowing site.
So this job was for my benefit, too.
Dieser Job war also auch zu meinem Vorteil.
I wanted to show my family my pride in my work.
Ich wollte meiner Familie zeigen, wie stolz ich auf meine Arbeit bin.
I'll repay them that way, as my brother said.
Ich werde es ihnen auf diese Weise zurückzahlen, wie mein Bruder sagte.
Thank you for telling me.
Danke, dass du es mir gesagt hast.
That honestly makes me very happy.
Das freut mich ehrlich gesagt sehr.
You didn't do your best only for me,
Du hast nicht nur für mich dein Bestes gegeben,
but for your own sake as well.
aber auch zu Ihrem eigenen Wohl.
I want us each to have our own goals
Ich möchte, dass jeder von uns seine eigenen Ziele hat
and support each other through the process,
und sich gegenseitig während des Prozesses unterstützen,
for the rest of our lives.
für den Rest unseres Lebens.
You warm me when I'm cold; I'll cool you when you're hot.
Du wärmst mich, wenn mir kalt ist; ich kühle dich, wenn dir heiß ist.
Like that, right?
So, oder?
Exactly.
Genau.
I prefer white. [Idee]
Ich bevorzuge Weiß. [Idee]
You prefer white? I'll go with blue.
Du bevorzugst Weiß? Ich nehme Blau.
Blue... I see.
Blau... ich verstehe.
- Idee, Hata speaking. - How about
- Idee, Hata spricht. - Wie wäre es mit
- Oh, hello. - this color?
- Oh, hallo. - diese Farbe?
- Yes. - Looks good.
- Ja. - Sieht gut aus.
- Ogata? One moment, please. - So this is the edge, right?
Einen Moment bitte. - Das ist also die Kante, richtig?
Kotori-san, Aiya's president on line 1 for you.
Kotori-san, Aiyas Präsident in Leitung 1 für Sie.
What? The president?
Was? Der Präsident?
Yes.
Ja.
Is something up?
Ist etwas los?
So sorry that you had to come.
Es tut mir so leid, dass Sie kommen mussten.
I wanted to thank you in person before I go to Kyoto.
Ich wollte mich persönlich bei Ihnen bedanken, bevor ich nach Kyoto fahre.
Thank me?
Danke mir?
Orders pour in since the website opened.
Seit der Eröffnung der Website gehen reihenweise Bestellungen ein.
Apparently, we trend on social media as well.
Offenbar sind wir auch in den sozialen Medien im Trend.
This is unprecedented.
Das ist beispiellos.
Is that so?
Ist das so?
Do you have a moment?
Haben Sie einen Moment Zeit?
Of course.
Natürlich.
I was actually always jealous of my brother.
Ich war eigentlich immer eifersüchtig auf meinen Bruder.
Though he was raised in the same household,
Obwohl er im selben Haushalt aufwuchs,
why was he given more freedom?
warum wurde ihm mehr Freiheit gegeben?
I found myself wishing for that freedom.
Ich ertappte mich dabei, wie ich mir diese Freiheit wünschte.
Now we've received orders from clients nationwide.
Mittlerweile haben wir Bestellungen von Kunden aus dem ganzen Land erhalten.
Sweets I take pride in bring joy to so many people.
Süßigkeiten, auf die ich stolz bin, bereiten so vielen Menschen Freude.
And I've realized, it makes me very happy, too.
Und ich habe festgestellt, dass es auch mich sehr glücklich macht.
Yes.
Ja.
Aiya's sweets have made me very happy, too.
Auch ich habe mich über die Süßigkeiten von Aiya sehr gefreut.
These are to thank you.
Diese sind als Dankeschön gedacht.
Thank you.
Danke schön.
Farewell then.
Dann leb wohl.
Gosh, these make me so happy! [Dorayaki]
Meine Güte, die machen mich so glücklich! [Dorayaki]
- Here. - Thanks.
- Hier. - Danke.
You take one, too, Soma-kun.
Nimm du auch eins, Soma-kun.
But you don't like them.
Aber du magst sie nicht.
I'll have one, too.
Ich nehme auch eins.
I think I'll like it now.
Ich glaube, es wird mir jetzt gefallen.
All right, let's dig in!
Also gut, legen wir los!
Yummy.
Lecker.
Our dorayaki is the best.
Unser Dorayaki ist das Beste.
Right?
Rechts?
But seeing your face as you eat these is the best.
Aber das Beste ist, Ihr Gesicht zu sehen, während Sie diese essen.
Oh, good.
Oh, gut.
The chief gave us a couple of days off to rest.
Der Chef gab uns ein paar Tage frei, damit wir uns ausruhen konnten.
This is great.
Das ist großartig.
So... any ideas for our long weekend?
Also ... irgendwelche Ideen für unser langes Wochenende?
Actually, can we go to a hot spring in Hakone?
Können wir eigentlich zu einer heißen Quelle in Hakone gehen?
A trip?
Eine Reise?
That means...
Das bedeutet...
W-We're staying the night?
W-Wir bleiben über Nacht?
I actually made reservations.
Ich habe tatsächlich reserviert.
What do you say?
Was sagen Sie?
Yes, let's go.
Ja, lass uns gehen.
"Stay the night"? What the heck, Soma!
„Über Nacht bleiben“? Was soll’s, Soma!
Kairi, why...
Kairi, warum ...
Your door was unlocked. Be more careful, Nee-chan.
Deine Tür war unverschlossen. Sei vorsichtiger, Nee-chan.
I'll watch that, but why are you here?
Ich werde mir das ansehen, aber warum bist du hier?
These are Mom's thanks for the sweets you sent.
Dies ist Mamas Dank für die Süßigkeiten, die du geschickt hast.
But listen, Soma! I'm coming on this trip with you!
Aber hör zu, Soma! Ich komme mit dir auf diese Reise!
You won't lay a finger on her.
Du wirst sie nicht anrühren.
Hey...
Hey...
Sure, go ahead. Right, Kotori-san?
Sicher, machen Sie weiter. Nicht wahr, Mr. Kotori?
Another day, another amazing tea.
Ein neuer Tag, ein neuer fantastischer Tee.
You think they'll bring back steamed sweet buns?
Glaubst du, sie werden gedämpfte süße Brötchen zurückbringen?
I want to go see the Northern Lights.
Ich möchte die Nordlichter sehen.
Maybe I'll go camping.
Vielleicht gehe ich zelten.
I recommend Yamanashi Prefecture.
Ich empfehle die Präfektur Yamanashi.
Oh, the lakes, right?
Oh, die Seen, richtig?
No reservation needed.
Keine Reservierung erforderlich.
- Oh yes, they're the best! - The best, right?
- Oh ja, sie sind die Besten! - Die Besten, oder?
- I want to go, too! - Me, too!
- Ich will auch gehen! - Ich auch!
Take us.
Nimm uns.
Let's all go.
Lasst uns alle gehen.
Sorry, I'm late.
Entschuldigen Sie, ich bin zu spät.
Did you wait long?
Hast du lange gewartet?
Don't worry. I just got here.
Keine Sorge, ich bin gerade erst angekommen.
Wait, where's Kairi-san?
Moment, wo ist Kairi-san?
He went home this morning,
Er ging heute Morgen nach Hause,
despite what he said.
trotz dem, was er gesagt hat.
Is it all fine?
Ist alles in Ordnung?
Yes, I'll make it up to him later.
Ja, ich werde es später wiedergutmachen.
Let's go, Soma-kun.
Lass uns gehen, Soma-kun.
"Ryosuke."
„Ryosuke.“
What?
Was?
Call me by my first name.
Nennen Sie mich bei meinem Vornamen.
♫ What makes you laugh? ♫
♫ Was bringt dich zum Lachen? ♫
♫ I want to be by your side ♫
♫ Ich möchte an deiner Seite sein ♫
Let's go, Ryosuke-kun.
Lass uns gehen, Ryosuke-kun.
Let's go, Kotori-san.
Los geht's, Mr. Kotori.
♫ Tell me I'm cute ♫
♫ Sag mir, dass ich süß bin ♫
♫ I put on the lipstick that's darker than usual ♫
♫ Ich trage einen Lippenstift auf, der dunkler ist als sonst ♫
Can't wait to go to Hakone.
Ich kann es kaum erwarten, nach Hakone zu fahren.
Yes, I can't wait!
Ja, ich kann es kaum erwarten!
I'm glad the weather's nice.
Ich bin froh, dass das Wetter schön ist.
I'm warm today.
Mir ist heute warm.
- Kotori and... - Ryosuke.
- Kotori und... - Ryosuke.
- The high body temp girl... - And the low body temp guy's...
- Das Mädchen mit der hohen Körpertemperatur ... - Und der Typ mit der niedrigen Körpertemperatur ...
- diaries!
- Tagebücher!
Welcome.
Willkommen.
Takeout, two medium coffees, please.
Zum Mitnehmen, zwei mittlere Kaffee, bitte.
Hot or iced?
Heiß oder eisgekühlt?
- Iced. - Hot.
- Eisgekühlt. - Heiß.
- Iced. Come on!
- Eiskalt. Komm schon!